巡逻队 出现橙色事件
Patrols, we got an Orange Situation.
卡森医生和神父失踪了
Dr. Carson and the priest.
可能是晚上走的 也可能是今早
Might've split overnight, maybe this morning.
杰里米的绿色轿车不见了 他们可能开着那辆车走的
Jeremy's green sedan is MIA, so could be in that.
在山顶寨周边范围
Go for standard search and cover.
进行常规搜查和掩护
in our perimeter around Hilltop.
眼睛睁大点
Eyeballs open.
巡逻四队收到
Patrol Four copies.
赶紧行动
‭C'mon, let's hurry it up.
最好别走马路 走这边的森林
Best to stay off the roads, head into the woods right there.
快 走 走
Come on. Go. Go.
我来
I got it.
我掩护你
I'll cover you.
塔拉
Tara!
干嘛 它挣脱开了
What? It got away.
他能应付
He can handle it.
我说吧
See?
让他们继续走
Hey. Just keep 'em moving.
我们走吧
Let's move out of here.
你听见他们在对讲机上说卡森和加百利的事了吗
Did you hear them talking on the walkie about Carson and Gabriel?
听见了 他们可能也去了山顶寨 和我们一样
Yeah. Probably heading to Hilltop, same as us.
希望比我们情况要好
Hopefully better than us.
你不知道我们在哪里吗
So, you have no idea where we are?
那得看情况
Well, that depends.
我们过了莱纳斯天桥吗
Have we passed the… "Linus Overpass" yet?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许昨晚过了 天很黑 我们…
I mean, maybe last night. It was dark. We…
你听见了吗
Did you hear that?
听见什么
Hear what?
你为什么…
Why are you…?
你一般戴眼镜吗
Do you normally wear glasses?
不 我只是
No. I j-just …
你视力模糊吗
Is your vision blurring?
如果感染影响了你的视神经
If this infection is attacking your optical nerves,
那可能永久损伤你的视力
it could permanently damage your eyesight. We …
我们在做我们应该做的事
We're doing what ‭we're supposed to be doing.
你应该为了玛姬回到山顶寨
And you're supposed to be back at the Hilltop for Maggie.
会没事的
It's going to be okay.
一切都会
All of it.
有点信念吧
Just have some faith.
我们在正确的道路上 就算这条路不对
We're on the right path, even if we're on the wrong road.
你有严重并发症 我们又迷路了 这很危险
Look. You have a serious complication, and we are dangerously lost.
你真觉得上帝在指引我们吗
Do you really think God is leading the way?
他一直都在指引我们
He's always leading the way.
很好
Great.
那很好
That's great.
也许我们该让他开会儿车
Well, maybe we should let Him drive for a little while.
我们应该敞开心灵接纳他
I mean, we should let him inside.
他的脚印一直都留在路边
Been leaving all those footprints along the side of the road.
《行尸走肉》
好 那边的英里标志牌呢
All right, what about that mile marker…right there?
从这里你能看见吗
Can you see that from here?
看不见
No.
真蠢
Stupid.
我真蠢 让你离开那里
I was stupid ‭to let you leave that place.
那你为什么要那样做
Then why did you?
因为你生病了
Because you're sick.
在山顶寨被洗劫之前
I stashed away ‭some antibiotics at the Hilltop.
我在那里藏了一些抗生素
before we were raided.
那药肯定还在那里
Well, then, there isn't any reason why they aren't still there.
我们找另一辆车
We'll find another car,
抵达山顶寨 然后…
we'll get there, and then we'll …
怎么了
What?
你听见了吗
You hear that?
听
There.
像是钟声
Almost like a bell.
我们不该冒险离开马路
We shouldn't risk leaving the road.
小心点
Look out.
是从上面传来的
It's coming from up here.
加百利
Gabriel!
不是钟 但这地方也许能拯救我们
It's not a bell, but this place may just be our salvation.
加百利 这地方看着拯救不了谁
Gabriel, this place does not scream salvation.
达里尔
Daryl.
他们人呢
Where are they?
他们需要休息
They needed rest.
他们都累坏了 一直没睡觉
They're exhausted. They haven't slept.
好吧 休息10分钟 然后上路
All right, 10 minutes. Then we keep goin'.
我往回走 把足迹掩盖起来
I'm gonna go back, cover our tracks.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
我有个问题
I have a question.
他还活着的原因是什么
Is there a reason why he's still breathing?
战斗还没有结束
Fight ain't over.
对他来说结束了
It is for him.
我等够了
I'm done waiting.
现在还不行
Not now. Not yet.
他说得对
He's right.
德怀特可能有我们不知道的信息
Dwight could have ‭an angle we don't know about.
他能帮忙 他也想帮忙
He could help. He wants to.
现在还不能放弃这一点
Can't give that up yet.
我们刚刚失去了那孩子
We just lost the kid.
不要再闹了
Let's just stop.
至少等到了山顶寨再说
At least until we get to the Hilltop.
我来接手吧 摩根
I can take over, Morgan.
不需要
Don't need to.
但也许你可以让亨利吃点东西
But maybe you can make Henry eat something.
我没事
I'm fine.
也许你能让他吃东西 我来接手
Maybe you can, and I can take over.
摩根
Morgan?
是叫摩根吧
It's Morgan, right?
这孩子怪吓人的
The kid is creeping people out.
也许你可以…让他走远点
Maybe you can, you know, move him along.
听着 你不想要他留在这里的
Listen, you don't want him here.
救世军会出现 把我们救出来
Saviors are gonna roll up and let us out,
到时候…场面可不好看
and, hell…it ain't gonna be pretty.
你们哪一个杀了我哥哥
Which one of you killed my brother?
去找杰瑞
Go find Jerry.
让他给你找点吃的
Tell him to get you something to eat.
但我不想…
But I don't wa…
我们为什么不告诉他
Why don't we tell him?
你知道为什么的
You know why.
他还是个孩子
He's a child.
他已经做了太多了
He's done too much already.
他会生存下去的 因为他知道该怎么做
He's gonna live 'cause he knows how.
他自己并不觉得困扰
Doesn't bother him.
他完全能接受
He's fine with it.
并没有
He's not.
只不过他现在还没意识到
He just doesn't know it yet.
他状态不好 摩根 你也一样
He's not fine, Morgan, and you aren't, either.
去休息一下吧
Take a break.
我很失望 尤金
I'm disappointed, Eugene.
这破事本该解决了
This crap was supposed to be behind us.
三下五除二的
Two flushes and out the pipe.
更过分的是
Top it all off,
我唯一的医生 以及那个瘆人的神父
my only doctor and that creepy-ass priest.
不知怎么地越狱成功了
somehow managed to jump ship.
还做得神不知鬼不觉
without anybody knowing about it.
你知道为什么会发生这种事吗 尤金
You have any idea how something like that could happen, Eugene?
不知道 我不敢乱猜
No, I would not venture to guess.
卡森和我们从来不是一条心
Carson was never one of us.
他很狡猾 和他那个狡猾的哥哥一样
He was a weasel, ‭just like his weasel brother.
这是我最靠谱的猜测
That's my best stab at it.
考虑到他俩的联系和行为…
Drawing together ‭associations and behaviors …
这个猜测很靠谱
that's a solid stab.
一旦他们被抓回这里…
Well, once their asses are caught and dragged back here …
这是一定的…
and they will be …
我会让他们一五一十全招了
I'm gonna get ‭the whole story out of 'em.
无论如何 我都会的
One way or another, yes, I will.
亚历山大呢 那里是什么情况
And Alexandria, what went down there?
你在乎吗
Do you care?
你在乎吗 尤金
Do you care, Eugene,
他们可是差点把你轰飞呢
after they tried to blow you off the face of this Earth?
你的信息已传达到并很受感激
Your message is stamped "Received" and very much appreciated.
是吗 很好
Oh, well, good.
那我要告诉你个消息 尤金
You see, I got some news for you, Eugene.
你将拥有自己全权负责的哨站
You are gonna be in charge of your very own outpost.
我需要我的子弹制造者制造子弹
You see, I need ‭my bullet maker making bullets.
从尸群里开路耗费了大量储备弹药
Cutting a path through the dead took a toll on our reserves.
所以现在你有幸为我
So now you get ‭the honors of providing me.
制造我需要的子弹
with the necessary bang-bang I'm gonna need.
好一次性解决瑞克问题
to settle this whole situation with Rick for good.
不是说人是资源吗
And all that about people being resources and whatnot?
子弹是最后手段
Bullets are the last resort.
我是说 妈的
I mean, hell,
露西尔有优先权
Lucille here, she gets first dibs.
但如果瑞克和他的混蛋小队
But if Rick ‭and his merry band of pricks.
决心要捣乱
decide to pull some shit,
那我们必须回击
then we're gonna ‭have to pull some right back.
即使我们不愿那么做
that we'd rather not.
那是他们的错
That'll be on them.
不是你的错 不是我的错
Not you. Not me.
我会把你安置在你曾提到过的机械车间里
I'm gonna set you up at that machine shop that you told me about.
你将拥有一支可供随时差遣的护卫队
You're gonna have a full security detail at your disposal.
以及你保持头脑清晰所需的一切
everything that you need to keep your head in the game.
让弗兰基帮你按摩
Got Frankie there giving you massages…
塔尼娅帮你烧菜
Tanya cooking.
知道吗 那姑娘曾是主厨
You know that gal was a chef?
我想象中她是搞社会科学的
I pictured her in social sciences.
管理人员
Management.
也许经营着窗帘厂
Maybe running a drapes factory.
那里有葡萄酒吗
Will there be wine?
必须有
There will, indeed.
安全吗
It's clear?
目前是
So far.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
看这上面写什么
Trying to read what this says.
你需要躺在沙发上
You need to be lying down on that couch.
能找到这地方已经很幸运了
You're lucky we found this place when we did.
跟运气没关系
Luck had nothing to do with this.
以前住在这的人
The person who lived here,
是无线电通讯员
they were a radio operator.
我们可以从这得知身在何处
It could tell us something about where we are.
「任何听到我声音的人
"To anyone who can hear my voice,
你不是孤单一人
know that you're not alone.
请坚持住
Please hold on.
只要不放弃 只要保持信念
We can make it through this if we don't give up.
就能撑过去「 只是个手稿而已
If we keep believing…" I mean, it's just a script.
- 对我们没帮助 - 也许吧
- It's not gonna help us. - Maybe not.
但似乎帮到过别人
But it sounds like it helped others.
你看 「没信号」「没信号」「没信号」
Look."No signal" "No signal" "No signal".
浏览一遍日志 我觉得没帮到过什么人
I mean, going by the logs, I don't think so.
但还是有可能帮过的
It still might have.
也许这人的信号被别人听到了
Maybe this person reached other people.
只是自己不知道
and never found out.
也许只是一遍遍说着这话
Maybe just by saying it over and over again,
让这人有了保持信念的理由
this person had reason to believe it.
让这人有了走下去的力量
Maybe it gave them the strength to go on,
就算没被别人听到过
even if they didn't reach anyone else.
好吧 不是那样的
Yeah, that didn't happen.
如果他们够聪明 就会看住这里
If they're smart, ‭they'll cover all these passes.
和山顶寨之间的所有路
between here and Hilltop.
我们得继续前进 必须冒这个险
We have to keep moving. We'll just have to risk it.
也许没必要
Maybe you don't have to.
尼根不会派人进入这片沼泽
Negan won't send his people down ‭into this stretch of swamp,
除非万不得已
not if he doesn't have to.
是吗 你怎么知道
Yeah? How do you know that?
尼根曾想找出从救世堂到山顶寨的
Negan wanted to map the best routes with cover.
最佳隐蔽路线
from the Sanctuary to the Hilltop.
他认为沼泽太危险了
He … He decided ‭the swamp was too dangerous.
不值得冒险
Didn't think it was worth the risk.
你们不会真打算听他的吧
You aren't seriously gonna listen to him.
这对救世军来说太危险了
It's too dangerous for the Saviors,
所以你们准备让我们去吗
so you're gonna send us?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我们已经被他们围住了
They have us boxed in.
塔拉说得对
Tara has a point.
我们为什么要相信他
Why should we trust him?
他可能会像背叛自己人一样背叛我们
He could turn on us like he turned on his own people.
我不仅背叛了他们
I didn't just turn on 'em.
我杀了他们
I killed 'em.
达里尔看到了
Daryl saw it.
罗西塔看到了
Rosita saw it.
你也看到了
You saw it.
但其中一个逃跑了
But one of them got away…
所以如果他们找到了我 尼根绝对会杀了我
So if they find me, Negan puts my head on a pike.
我不为他们做事了 我也不会回去找他们
I'm not working for them, and I'm not going back to them.
我选择了我的阵营 那就是这里
I chose my side. This is it.
我是来帮你们打倒尼根的
I'm here to help you beat Negan.
之后 我知道会有什么下场
After that… well, I know how it ends.
好啊
All right.
我们试试从沼泽走
We try the swamps.
伯蒂和我清点完了
Bertie and I finished the inventory.
有多糟
How bad?
根据我们的清点 你得再削减三分之一的配给
By our count, you're gonna have to cut rations by another third.
才能撑过这礼拜
just to make it through the week.
人数包括囚犯吗
This number include the prisoners?
如果包括囚犯的话得削减更多
It's worse if you include the prisoners.
耶稣还在外面搜刮
Jesus is still out scavenging.
他也许会带回来些什么
He could bring back something.
我说了 你得躺下
I told you … ‭you need to be lying down.
我没事
I'm fine.
加百利 你必须听我的
Gabriel, you have to listen to me.
你的感染很严重
You are fighting a serious infection.
你必须躺着…
And you need to be in there …
你看得出这两瓶是什么吗
Can you read what any of these are?
怎么了
What?
都是抗生素
These are both antibiotics.
这人可能救了你的命
This man may have just saved your life.
我一句话都不说了
I'm not saying a word.
即使成功了 也没什么改变
This works, it don't change shit.
我所做的一切都是为了雪莉
Everything I did, it was for Sherry.
这不代表那就是对的
That doesn't make it right.
或者你们应该原谅我
Or something that should be forgiven.
但这是事实
But it's the truth.
我仅剩的寄托
Only one I got left.
是她放你出来的 然后她逃走了
She's the one that let you out. Then she ran.
她在外面吗
She's out here?
在某个地方
Somewhere.
但愿吧
I hope.
我们必须小心
We have to be careful,
但我们可以的
but we can do this.
往前走 给其他人清出一条路来
Push through. Clear a path for the others.
加我一个
Count me in.
我也去
I'll go.
如果能给我弩
If I can have the crossbow …
不行 待在那儿别动
You can't. You'll stay right there.
你来吗
You coming?
我殿后 照顾大家
I'm gonna hang back, watch over the group.
走吧 赶紧搞定
Come on. Let's get this done.
玛格丽特 谢谢你和我说话
Margret. ‭Thank you for speaking with me.
你想要什么 格雷戈里
What do you want, Gregory?
我知道我们看法向来不一致
I know we haven't exactly seen eye-to-eye on anything.
质疑过忠诚 推卸过责任
Loyalties have been questioned, fingers have been pointed…
抛开这些不谈 你得承认
All of that aside, you have to admit.
你把我关在这以来
that, since you threw me in here,
我都表现得很好
my behavior has been pretty good.
你不能出来 格雷戈里
You're staying in, Gregory.
什么
What?
都不听我把话说完吗
So you're not gonna hear me out?
你不能永远把我关在这
You can't just leave me in here forever.
给我一个理由杀了你 就不用了
Give me a reason to kill you, and I won't have to.
他说得对
He's right, you know.
我们一直很听话
We've been good.
你叫我们做的 我们都做了
We've done everything you've told us to do.
然而昨晚 你还是杀了我们其中一人
And still, last night, you took one of us out and …
我知道自己做了什么
Yeah, I know what I did.
好吧
Okay.
你把我们当敌人对待得越久
The longer you treat us like the enemy,
- 我们就会表现得越… - 你们就是敌人
- the more we're gonna act… - You are the enemy.
我认为我们不必当敌人
I don't think we have to be.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
表现好的人能出来放风
Time outside the pen for good behavior.
每次一人 每天几分钟
You know, one at a time, a couple minutes a day,
到阴凉处待一会 做做运动
some … some shade, exercise.
你想用多少枪指着我们都行
You can have ‭all the guns on us you like.
你怎么说
What do you say?
我没有资源满足你
I don't have ‭the resources to oblige you,
就算我想
even if I wanted to.
所以就这样了
So, that's it, then?
不
No.
我要停止供给你们食物
I'm cutting off your rations.
几天 也许更久
A few days, maybe longer.
- 什么 - 玛姬
- What? - Maggie…
我的人最重要
My people come first.
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
我想你有
I think you do.
或许我们可以绕过去
Maybe we can go around?
最浅的河段就在前面
The shallowest spot's straight ahead.
我们把行尸全干掉 人就能过去
We clear 'em out. That's how we get our people through.
- 准备好了吗 - 好了
- You ready? - ‭Yeah.
谁想帮我杀掉那只行尸
Who wants to help me take care of that?
恭喜 你刚毛遂自荐了
Congratulations. You just volunteered.
你的烧好像退了
Well…your fever appears to have broken…
但你的视力…
But your eyesight…
如果短期内没有改善
Well, if there's not some improvement soon,
恐怕就是永久损伤了
I'm afraid you're looking at permanent damage.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我能活下来 你感到遗憾吗
You're sorry I'm going to live?
你懂我意思
You know what I mean.
在这种环境下失去视觉
Losing your vision. In this.
这个念头难道不让你害怕吗
The thought of that doesn't scare you?
或是让你生气 哪怕只有一点
Or…piss you off, even a little bit?
我让上帝指引我前行
I'm letting Him lead the way.
我虽然看不见
I can't even see it,
但我能感觉到你脸上的表情
but I can feel the look on your face.
我不是说 是上帝指引我们来这里
I'm not saying ‭God led us to this place.
让我们玩什么寻宝游戏
That this is some scavenger hunt He's put us on.
而是说 要在此刻寻找意义
But to search ‭for meaning in this moment.
只需环顾四周
simply by looking around…
或是感受…
Or … Or feeling …
不会吧
You gotta be shitting me.
怎么了
What?
是车钥匙和地图
It's car keys and a map.
我看看
Here we go…
巴灵顿之家生活历史博物馆
Barrington House Living History Museum.
我们只偏离了几英里
We … We can't be more than a few miles off.
你可以用刀掩护我
You could cover me with the knife.
是可以 但我要用枪掩护你
I could, but I'm covering you with this.
最后一只
Last one.
你确定不杀吗
Sure you don't want it?
浪费颗子弹吗 不用了谢谢
And waste a bullet? No thanks.
丹妮斯的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about Denise.
我是真心的 我不奢望你原谅我
I truly am. I don't expect you to forgive me.
我不配
I don't deserve it.
我只想要你知道 就这样
I just wanted you to know, that's all.
你应该和救世军留在一起
You should've stayed with the Saviors.
我恨他们
I hate 'em.
我恨尼根
I hate Negan.
我不在乎
Don't care.
你不能换了阵营 当什么事都没发生过
You don't get to switch sides and make it okay.
我知道我不能
I know I don't.
永远都不能
I never will.
但现在这样杀了我
But killing me right now, like this…
又有什么用呢
What's that gonna do?
会让我感觉好很多
It's gonna make me feel a hell of a lot better.
我知道会这样的
I knew it was gonna happen.
我只想先帮你们赢下来
I just wanted to help you win first.
我是说他们不会蠢到来冒险的
‭Just sayin' they'd be idiots to risk it is all.
至少可以说我们搜过了
Least we can say we checked…
总比莫尼的差事好
Still rather be us than J-Money right now.
希望车还在车库里
Let's hope the car's actually in the garage.
在的
It is.
危险
院内有陷阱
卡森医生 停下 等等
Dr. Carson! Stop! Wait!
你做到了
You … You … You did it.
我可能得到了一些帮助
I think I might have had some help.
沼泽在那边 我们抄近路过去
The swamp's that way. Let's cut through there.
德怀特
Dwight?
你怎么了
The hell happened to you?
我们以为你死了
We thought you were dead!
当时有埋伏
It was an ambush.
我们几乎被全歼 但我逃出来了
You know, they shot us to hell, but I got away.
一晚上都在东躲西藏
‭Spent the whole night hiding…
你们知道的 躲着行尸
You know, ‭running from the dead ones…
试着回去
Trying to make it back.
劳拉怎么样了
What happened to Laura?
我想她可能也跑出来了
I thought she might made it out, too.
抱歉 小德
Yeah, I'm sorry, D.
没人见过她
No one's seen her.
那你们在这做什么呢
So, what are you doing out here?
追踪亚历山大那群人
Trackin' the Alexandrians.
想去沼泽探探 看能找到些什么
'Bout to check the swamp, see what we can see.
我刚从那边过来
I just came from there.
他们很聪明 没去那里
They were smart enough to steer clear.
现在 如果我是他们
Now, if I were them,
我会待在伯克斯小道附近
I'd stick closer to Burke's Pass.
隐蔽性更好 路更近
Good cover, straighter shot.
好 带路吧 小德
Yeah. Yeah, lead the way, D.
你没穿你的背心 几乎没认出来你
Barely recognized you without your vest.
还好我们没打你
Lucky we didn't shoot your ass.
你在做什么
What were you doing?
确保你没事
Making sure you were okay.
我看到你追他了
I saw you running after him.
你为什么不阻止我
Why didn't you try and stop me?
当时也没人能阻止我
No one could've stopped me.
我要你等着
I told you to wait!
说不定他已经全告诉他们了
For all we know, he could be telling them everything!
尼根可能已经在来的路上了
Negan could be on his way here right now!
他没有 他不会的
He isn't. He won't.
他把他们引走了
He led them away.
他们是冲着我们的方向来的 他救了我们
They were coming right for us, and he saved us.
她说得对 他救了我们 我看到了
She's right. He did. I saw it.
我不在乎他做了什么
I don't give a damn what he did.
他可以和他们待在一起
He can stick with them,
他可以回来 妈的 可以逃跑
he can come back … hell, he can run.
等我找到那个贱种 我就…
When I find that son of a bitch, I'm gonna …
走吧
C'mon.
你确定不要我开车吗
You, uh, sure you don't want me to drive?
我真的不介意
I really don't mind.
我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
举起手来 混蛋
Hands up, assholes.
他们一定是听见枪声了
They must've heard the gunfire.
上帝依然在指引我们
He's still leading the way.
相信这点 你就能看到前路
Believe it, and you'll see it.
我想我看到了
I think I do see it.
拜托 那可是医生 可恶
C'mon, man! ‭That's the doctor, damn it!
我们惨了
That's our asses.
快他妈拿枪上车
Get your damn gun, and get in the cab.
不
No.
我们走吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
不
No.
他怎么死的
How did he die?
是他们干的吗
Was it them?
他当时在帮助陌生人
He was helping a stranger.
在这种情况下 他仍在帮助陌生人
In the middle of all this, he was helping a stranger.
你问你哥哥
You asked about your brother.
是谁杀的
Who killed him.
是加文
It was Gavin.
你杀了他 所以
And you got him, so…
抱歉
Sorry.
我只想感谢你接纳我
Just wanted to thank you for your hospitality.
这没什么
It's not much.
你错了
You're wrong.
这是一切
It's everything.
你这里有医院 诊所之类的地方吗
Do you have a hospital here, some kind of infirmary?
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
不 我没事
No, I'm fine.
只是 我有些医疗经验
I just…have some medical experience.
想着我能做点贡献 帮帮忙
Thought I could pitch in and help.
在拖车里
In the trailers.
谢谢你
Thank you.
瞧瞧你 大人物
Well, look at you, Mr. Big Shot.
这是你命中注定要做的事
You were destined for this.
生产线上必须戴手套和护眼
Nobody on the line without gloves and proper eye protection.
我只想帮忙
I just thought I could help.
要不你教我做颗子弹
Maybe you could show me how to make one.
你可以帮我点餐
You can help ‭by taking my dinner order,
用长距离对讲机转告塔尼娅
relaying it to Tanya via the longrange.
鸡蛋就可以 加上点番茄
Eggs will do nicely. Dancing with tomatoes.
一份番茄卷蛋 没问题
One tomato omelet … you got it.
别卷 要炒碎
No fold over. I'm talkin' a scramble.
给我的团队多来几份
Several of them, actually. For my crew.
不要番茄 要辣椒 多放点
No damn tomatoes. Peppers, lots of 'em.
有放多少放多少
As many as you got.
你听到了
You heard the man.
我想把食堂设在这里
And I'd like said repast set up over here,
西北角 我在此正式宣布
in the Northwest corner, which I hereby.
此处为车间食堂 休息室
designate as this workplace's official cafeteria, break room,
兼动员室
and motivational presentational cubby.
而且我稍后需要人给我的额头擦汗
And my brow will soon be in need of wiping.
看看我找到了谁
Lookee what I found.
他给我讲了一个很有趣的故事
And he told me a very interesting story.
关于他是怎么逃出我们温馨之家的
about how he made his way out of our lovely home.
是卡森帮我的
It was Carson.
我早说了吧
Did I call it or what?
我很高兴
I am agog.
但为什么带他来这里
But why bring him here?
你需要人手分拣弹壳对吧
Well, you need an extra set of hands to sort out ‭those bullet casings, right?
显然他眼睛什么也看不清
Apparently, his eyes don't work for shit,
但他有手
but he does have a set of hands.
我们先试用吧
We'll see if it helps.
我现在只有少量弹药
I only have a few bullets as it is …
质量很高 但数量不足
quality munitions, but the quantity is full-on scant.
所以要想得到弹药补给 还得几天
It's still gonna be a few more days before we have any sort of supply to speak of.
尤金
See, Eugene…
这样可不行
that simply doesn't work for me.
我想我们可以
I think a more biblical approach.
用古战法制造最大的恐惧
for maximum fright may be in order.
我们可以搭几台中世纪投石器
We could rig several medieval-style catapults,
将行尸四肢和躯干投入敌防区内
start launching undead arms, legs, torsos over their defenses,
也可以是头颅或内脏
maybe heads or, you know, big piles of guts.
纯心理战
You know, pure psych-ops.
造成极大的心理创伤
I mean, there's some really traumatic theatrics there.
谢谢
Thank you.
粪堆里刚开出了一朵玫瑰
I do believe a rose just sprang out of that pile of shit.
走吧
Let's roll.
明天是个大日子
Big day tomorrow.
我以为
I thought …
我以为我找到了
I thought I found it.
我命中注定要做的事
What I was meant to do …
你找到了
You have.
我也找到了
So have I.
开始分拣吧
Now get sortin'.
速度快点
Let's pick up the pace.
囚犯将成对外出放风
Prisoners will be taken out in pairs,
在武装守卫的看守下
under armed guard,
工作 运动 如有必要的话 接受治疗
for work, exercise, and, if necessary, medical attention.
你们先开始清理畜舍
You'll start by cleaning the stables.
食物呢
What about food?
四分之一配给
Quarter rations …
- 和我们一样 - 玛格丽特
- same as all of us. - Margret …
别说逼我关你回去的话
Don't say anything that'll make me put you back in there.
不 我很感激 真的
No. I-I appreciate this. I-I do.
救世军依然会来
The Saviors are still coming.
食物所剩无几
Barely any food left,
补给非常稀少
supplies just stretched out to nothing.
也许我们该考虑一下撤离
M-Maybe we ought to consider evacuation.
撤离
Evacuation?
是的 我们逃跑 活下去
Yeah. We run, we live.
我是说 我们怎么可能赢
I mean…how can we win?
看看周围 格雷戈里
Look around, Gregory.
我们怎么可能输
How can we lose?
开门 是瑞克
Open the gates! It's Rick!
你们知道是怎么回事
You all know how it works.
被咬一口
You get a bite,
或者被它们搞伤
some kind of wound from one of these things,
你会被感染 然后死掉
something from them gets in you, and you die.
加入不死大军
You join the club…
这很糟
which sucks.
但如果我们能利用这点呢
What if we could use that to our advantage?
看到露西尔是怎么和我们
Ah, you see how Lucille is getting to know.
美丽冰冷的朋友亲热的吗
our beautiful, cold friend here?
对
That's it.
看看
Look…at…that.
不用再敲敲打打
No more smashing and bashing.
有了这个 只用轻轻碰一下
With this … Well, this, it can just be a touch.
或者湿吻一个
Or a big, wet kiss.
不管哪样 你都会直接加入它们
Either way, this gets you full membership,
这就是我们的目标
and that's what we want.
我们要让他们加入不死大军
We want people to join the club.
山顶寨会学会遵守规矩
Hilltop is gonna learn to toe the line one way or another,
不论生或死
dead or alive…
或他妈半死不活
…or some kinda shit in between.